//arrays
const questions = [
  { question: "The following are all Mondstadt characters except", answer: 4 },
  { question: "What is the Vigilant Yaksha's true name?", answer: 2 },
  { question: "Diluc, owner of the Dawn Winery, prefers to drink", answer: 2 },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is NOT one of the four winds?",
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "During the Archon war, which god was slain by their own people?",
    answer: 1,
  },
  { question: "What caused the fall of Sal Vindagnyr?", answer: 3 },
  {
    question: "When deciphered, in what language is the lost language written?",
    answer: 3,
  },
  { question: "What secret is Celestia hiding from humanity?", answer: 2 },
  { question: "What is the name of the Unknown God?", answer: 1 },
  { question: "What are the stars?", answer: 1 },
];

//other constants
//const chOne = document.querySelector("#choice1");

//not the constants

//testing functions
//chOne.addEventListener("click", pressButtonOne);

//function pressButtonOne() {
//  console.log("pressed button one");

//real deal

//function replaceQuestion() {}

//function replaceAnswer() {}

const chOne = document.getElementById("ch1");
chOne.potato = ["lemons", 3];
